A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Detlev Bronk, Personal and Professional papers FA965
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal and professional papers
  - DWB Personal, 1951-1972
    - Bronk Correspondence, 70th Birthday, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Bronk Correspondence, Birthday Greetings, 1949-1974 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Bronk Correspondence and Addresses, Retirement from Rockefeller University, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Club and Organizational Correspondence, 1926-1964 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Club and Organizational Correspondence, 1965-1975 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Bronk Correspondence, Illness, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Bronk Correspondence, 75th Birthday, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Bronk Correspondence, 50th Wedding Anniversary, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Century Club, 1958-1964 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Century Club and Oskar Morgenstern, 1965-1974 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Cosmos Club, 1954-1962 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Cosmos Club, 1963-1974 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Lotus Club, 1956-1973 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - University Club, 1954-1959 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - University Club, 1960-1975 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Wistar Association, 1953-1968 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Bronk Correspondence, Books from Friends, 1955-1963 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Bronk Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1954-1966 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - DWB Personal, Rockefeller Family Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Books for Library, 1954-1975
    - Correspondence, Peggy and David Rockefeller, 1954-1969 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Peggy and David Rockefeller, 1970-1975 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, David Rockefeller Family, 1959-1974 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Family Correspondence, 1958-1969 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Miscellaneous, 1954-1965 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1958-1975 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Correspondence, Seal Harbor, Maine, 1957-1975 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, Rockefeller Brothers Fund, General Education Board, 1934-1961 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Invitations, Declinations, 1957-1960 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Invitations, Declinations, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Invitations, Declinations, 1960-1961 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Invitations, Declinations, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Invitations, Declinations, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Invitations, Declinations, 1964-1975 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Books for Library I, undated (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Books for Library II, undated (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Books for Library III, undated (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Books for Library IV, undated (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Books for Library V, undated (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Books for Library VI, undated (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Engagement Books, 1948-1975 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - American Geological Institute, Lectures, NAS, Reprints of Bronk Articles, John F. Fulton re Joseph Priestley, 1928-1975
    - American Geological Institute, 1949-1950 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - American Geological Institute, 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - American Geological Institute, Printed Materials, 1942-1972 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Bartram Lecture, Florida State University, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Croonian Lecture, The Royal Society, 1949 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Fulton, John F., re Priestley, Joseph, Manuscripts, 1938 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Fulton, John F., re Priestley, Joseph, Correspondence, 1933-1938 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Fulton, John F., re Priestley, Joseph, Printed Materials, 1933-1937 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Harvey Lectures, 1934 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Mellon Institute, 1960 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Riddle Memorial Hospital, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Sigma Xi, 1943 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - National Academy of Science, Academy Building Article, 1972-1975 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - NAS, Notes and Historical Background, 1962-1973 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - New Lands, New Spheres, Cocraine, Rexmond C., 1969 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - National Academy of Science, Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - National Academy of Science, Hale, George Ellery, undated (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - NAS, Archives, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - NAS, History, Ruth Ingles, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - NAS, History, Frank Jewett, 1947 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - NAS, History, Howard Lewis, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - National Academy of Sciences (Box 86, Folder 23)
      1963-1963, Author unknown.
    - NAS, Officers and Council Members, 1963-1963 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - NAS, Printed Materials I, 1922-1971 (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - NAS, Printed Materials II, 1947-1959 (Box 86, Folder 26)
    - NAS, Printed Material, 1967-1968 (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - Manuscript, The Nobel Prize in Physiology and Medicine in 1932 (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - Ms, The Sympathetic Control of the Heart, 1933-1934 (Box 86, Folder 29)
    - Ms, The Nervous Regulation of Blood Pressure, 1934 February 1 (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - Ms, The Nervous Regulation of the Heart, 1935 January 22 (Box 86, Folder 31)
    - Ms, Rhythms in the Sympathetic Nervous System, circa 1935 (Box 86, Folder 32)
    - Ms, The Social Significance of Intellectual Leadership, 1937 (Box 86, Folder 33)
    - Ms, Radio Address, 1938 (Box 86, Folder 34)
    - Ms, Statement by DWB, 1945 October 24 (Box 86, Folder 35)
    - Ms, Croonian Lecture, The. Royal Society, 1949 (Box 86, Folder 36)
    - Dedication Ceremony of the Hospital for Special Surgery, New York City, 1955 September 29 (Box 86, Folder 37)
    - Citation of John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1959 May 22 (Box 86, Folder 38)
    - Alfred Newton Richards, 1876-1966 1971 (Box 86, Folder 39)
    - Rockefeller University Convocation, 1960 (Box 86, Folder 40)
    - A National Focus of Science and Research, 1971 April 26 (Box 86, Folder 41)
    - Introduction to the W.J.V. Osterhout Memorial Lecture, 1971 July 23 (Box 86, Folder 42)
    - Ms, Using of the Geological Sciences, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 43)
    - Ms, Bartram Lecture, Florida State University, 1944 January 16 (Box 86, Folder 44)
    - Abstracts and Manuscripts, 1933-1935 (Box 86, Folder 45)
    - Ms, Willard Gibbs, undated (Box 86, Folder 46)
    - Graphs and Charts, 1933 (Box 86, Folder 47)
    - Reprint of Bronk Article, 1938 (Box 86, Folder 48)
    - Reprints of Bronk Articles, 1944 (Box 86, Folder 49)
    - Reprints of Bronk Articles, 1945-1946 (Box 86, Folder 50)
    - Reprints of Bronk Articles, 1946-1947 (Box 86, Folder 51)
    - Reprint of Bronk Article, 1948 (Box 86, Folder 52)
    - Reprint of Bronk Article, 1949 November 22 (Box 86, Folder 53)
    - Reprint of Bronk Article, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 54)
    - Reprint of Bronk Article, 1951 (Box 86, Folder 55)
    - Case Diamond Jubilee Convocation, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 56)
    - Reprint of Bronk Article, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 57)
    - The Council of State Governments, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 58)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration Chronology, 1945-1970 (Box 86, Folder 59)
    - University of Michigan, Kresge Medical Research Bldg. Dedication, 1954 May 15 (Box 86, Folder 60)
    - Physiological Society, Program, 1928 (Box 86, Folder 61)
    - U.S. Military Academy, West Point, Jubilee Convocation, 1952 (Box 86, Folder 62)
    - Graduate Research Center of the Southwest, Annual Report, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 63)
    - National Academy of Science, Pamphlet, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 64)
    - NAS, Pamphlets, 1952-1972 (Box 86, Folder 65)
    - National Science Foundation, Pamphlet, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 66)
    - University of the State of New York, Office of Science and Technology, Pamphlet, 1971 April (Box 86, Folder 67)
    - International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology, Pamphlet, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 68)
    - Association of American Universities, Pamphlet, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 69)
  - Personal Correspondence - E.D. Adrian, A.V. Hill, Ali M. and André Monnier, A. Newton Richards, Alexander von Muralt, 1926-1975
    - Adrian, E.D., Correspondence, 1926-1930 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Adrian, E.D., Correspondence, 1931-1934 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Adrian, E.D., Correspondence, 1935-1943 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Adrian, E.D., Correspondence, 1947-1955 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Adrian, E.D., Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Adrian, E.D., Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Adrian, E.D., Correspondence, 1949-1964 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Adrian, E.D., Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Adrian, E.D., Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Adrian, E.D., Miscellaneous, 1958-1975 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Adrian, E.D., Nobel Prize, 1932 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Adrian, E.D., Publications, 1931-1956 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Adrian Family, Correspondence, 1926-1955 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Adrian Family, Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Adrian Family, Correspondence, 1961-1975 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Hill, A.V., Correspondence, 1928-1954 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Hill, A.V., Correspondence, 1951-1959 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Hill, A.V., Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Hill, A.V., Correspondence, 1966-1975 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Hill, A.V. and Margaret Hill,, Memorabilia, 1923-1962 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Monnier, Ali M. and André, Correspondence, 1930-1961 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Monnier, Ali M. and André, Correspondence, 1962-1975 (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - Bronk's Physiological Laboratory Notes, 1928 February-October (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Richards, A. Newton, Correspondence, 1929-1959 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - Richards, A. Newton, Correspondence, 1960-1968 (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - Richards, A. Newton, re Biographical Memoir, 1966-1972 (Box 87, Folder 26)
    - Richards, A. Newton, re Biographical Memoir, 1972-1975 (Box 87, Folder 27)
    - von Muralt, Alexander, Correspondence, 1948-1960 (Box 87, Folder 28)
    - von Muralt, Alexander, Correspondence, 1962-1975 (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - DWB Reprints, 1923-1976
    - Reprints, 1923-1929 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Reprints, 1930-1934 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Reprints, 1935-1939 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Reprints, 1940-1945 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Reprints, 1946-1951 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Reprints, 1952-1957 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Reprints, 1958-1961 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Reprints, 1962-1970 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Reprints, 1971-1976 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Reprints, 1970-1976 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Studies in Early Graduate Education, Johns Hopkins, 1939 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Cassette Tape re National Medal of Science, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Biographical Chronology, Honorary Degrees, 1897-1970s; 2 3 × 5 Boxes (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - NRC, Programs, Addresses, Conference, 1921-1972
    - American Geological Institute, Newsletter, 1949 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - American Institute of Biological Science, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Arthur Dehon Little Memorial Lectureship, 1949 November 22 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - "Aviation Medicine, " Address, 1945 January 28 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Conference of State Academies of Science, 1950 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Conference on Population Problems, Documentation, 1952 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Conference on Population Problems, Documentation, 1952 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - David Rockefeller, Correspondence, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Rosenfeld, Harry N., Correspondence, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - University of PA, Division of Biophysics, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - "An Electrometric Study of the Submaxillary Gland of the Dog, " Draft, undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Faraday Celebrations, 1931 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Bronk Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Bronk Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Indian Science Congress Association, Delegation, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - International Center of Insect Physiology and Ecology, Report, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - International Congress of Experimental Cytology, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Army-Navy-NRC Vision Committee, Minutes and Proceedings, 1947 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Army-Navy-NRC Vision Committee, Minutes and Proceedings, 1947 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Notes and Lectures, 1921 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - National Research Council (NRC), 1946 (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - NRC, 1947 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - NRC, 1948-1949 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - NRC, Committee on Aviation Medicine, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - NRC, Committee on Merck Awards, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - NRC, Committee on Prosthetic Devices, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Neurobiology Survey Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - "Outline of the More General Methods Employed in Solution of Ordinary Differential Equations", undated (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - Pauling, Linus, 1955-1963 (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - Photographs of Charts and Graphs, undated (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Programs, 1949-1951 (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - Programs, 1952-1953 (Box 89, Folder 32)
    - Swarthmore College, Senior Oration, undated (Box 89, Folder 33)
    - Bronk Thesis, Draft, undated (Box 89, Folder 34)
    - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 35)
    - University of Michigan, Commencement, 1926 (Box 89, Folder 36)
    - Villa Serbelloni, Nobel Workshop on Institutions for Development, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 37)
    - Villa Serbelloni, An International Federation of Institutes for Advanced Study, A Feasibility Study, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 38)
    - World Academy of Art and Science, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - DWB Scrapbooks, 1855-1964
    - Scrapbook, Bronk Family History, DWB Personal History to 1950, 1855-1950 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      Original scrapbooks are closed to scholarly research due to their brittle condition. Photocopied versions are available for researcher access.
    - Scrapbook, Atomic Bomb, Radiation, Loyalty Checks, Polio Vaccine, Space Satellites, 1955-1956 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, Atoms for Peace, Eisenhower Campaign, 1955-1956 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook, Cancer Research, Polio Vaccine, Rockefeller Brothers, Rockefeller Institute, "Radio Pill", 1953-1957 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Century Fund Lecture, 1950 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Original is closed to scholarly research due to its brittle condition. Photocopied versions are available for researcher access.
    - Holiday Magazine, (bound copy), 1964 September (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Scrapbook (photocopy), Bronk Family History, DWB Personal History to 1950, 1855-1950 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook (photocopy), Atomic Bomb, Radiation, Loyalty Checks, Polio Vaccine, Space Satellites, 1955-1956 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook (photocopy), Atoms for Peace, Eisenhower Campaign, 1955-1956 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook (photocopy), Cancer Research, Polio Vaccine, Rockefeller Brothers, Rockefeller Institute, "Radio Pill", 1953-1957 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Century Fund Lecture, 1950 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Biographical sketch, 1855-1964
    - Bronk Biographical Sketch, 1897-1949 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1951 1953 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Bronk Personal Correspondence, 1948-1953 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence-B, 1940 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence-B, 1940 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Unidentified Signatures, 1940-1975 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1949-1959 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - British Association for the Advancement of Science, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - International Geophysical Year, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Johns Hopkins University, Homecoming Weekend, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Johns Hopkins University. Henry Allen Moe, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Johns Hopkins University, DWB Addresses, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Johns Hopkins University, DWB Addresses, 1950-1952 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, Loyalty Clearance, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - University of PA, Correspondence, 1936-1949 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - University of PA, Celebration of Medical Progress, 1930 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - University of PA. Bicentennial, 1940 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - University of PA, Address, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - DWB Address, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1950-1958 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Memorabilia, Doodles, undated (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - The Old Mistresses' Apologue, Benjamin Franklin, 1745 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - The Lowdown on Higher Education, Joel H. Hildebrand, 1948 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Medical Progress at the University of PA, Report, 1930 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Card Index Boxes, 1745-1975 (Box 92)
  - Card Index Boxes (Box 97, Box 95, Box 96, Box 93, Box 94)
  - Citations, Awards, Photographs, Honorary Degrees, 1918-1968 (Box 98)
  - Awards, Honorary Degrees, Flyers, 1954-1974 (Box 99)
  - Photographs, Correspondence, 1908-1974 (Box 100)
  - Certificates, Charts, Diplomas, 1911-1972 (Box 101)
  - DWB and Mitchell Bronk Scrapbooks, 1900-1958
    Original scrapbooks are closed to scholarly research due to their brittle condition. Photocopied versions are available in Box 103 for researcher access.
    - Detlev W. Bronk Scrapbook, Newspaper Clippings, 1954-1958 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Mitchell Bronk Scrapbook, Articles, Writings, 1914-1949 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Mitchell Bronk Scrapbook, Articles, Writings, 1900-1910 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - DWB and Mitchell Bronk Scrapbooks (photocopies), 1900-1958
    - Detlev W. Bronk Scrapbook (photocopy), 1954-1958 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Mitchell Bronk Scrapbook (photocopy, 1914-1949 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Mitchell Bronk Scrapbook (photocopy, 1900-1910 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Densograph Readings, 1937-1941
    - Gang Trans, 1937 January 22 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 January 26 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 February 12 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 March 12 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 March 20 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 May 5 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 May 12 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 May 18 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 June 11 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 June 28 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1937 June 30 (Box 104)
    - Gang Trans, 1939 May 11 (Box 104)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 9 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 11 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 14 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 16 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 23 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 25 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 31 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 November 7 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 November 14 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 2 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 10 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 13 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 18 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 26 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1941 January 9 (Box 105)
    - Distension of Lungs, 1941 January 14 (Box 105)
    - Distension of Lungs, 1941 January 21 (Box 105)
    - Distension of Lungs, 1941 January 21 (Box 105)
    - Distension of Lungs, 1941 January 24 (Box 105)
    - Distension of Lungs, 1941 February 4 (Box 105)
    - Distension of Lungs, 1941 March 14 (Box 105)
    - Distension of Lungs, 1941 March 24 (Box 105)
    - Distension of Lungs, 1941 April 2 (Box 105)
    - Vagal Afferents, 1941 May 7 (Box 105)
    - Vagal Afferents, 1941 May 8 (Box 105)
    - Vagal Afferents, 1941 May 15 (Box 105)
    - Vagal Afferents, 1941 May 28 (Box 105)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 14 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 21 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 October 25 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 November 22 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 4 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 6 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 13 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 18 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1940 December 26 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1941 January 7 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1941 January 16 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1941 January 30 (Box 106)
    - Respiratory Center, 1941 April 7 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 February 1 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 February 3 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 February 8 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 February 10 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 February 11 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 February 19 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 February 21 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 February 25 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 March 1 (Box 106)
    - Afferents Vagus, 1941 March 3 (Box 106)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), National Science Board (NSB), 1951-1954
    - National Science Foundation, (NSF), National Science Board (NSB), Agenda, 6th Meeting, 1951 May (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 7th Meeting, 1951 July (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 8th Meeting, 1951 September (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 8th Meeting, 1951 September (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 9th Meeting, 1951 October (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 10th Meeting, 1951 December (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 11th Meeting, 1952 February 1-2 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 12th Meeting, 1952 February 29 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 13th Meeting, 1952 April (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 14th Meeting, 1952 June (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 14th Meeting, 1952 June (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 15th Meeting, 1952 August (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 16th Meeting, 1952 October (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 17th Meeting, 1952 December (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 18th Meeting, 1953 January (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 18th Meeting, 1953 January (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 19th Meeting, 1953 March (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 20th Meeting, 1953 May (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 21st Meeting, 1953 July (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 22nd Meeting, 1953 August (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 23rd Meeting, 1953 October (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 24th Meeting, 1953 December (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 24th Meeting, 1953 December (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 25th Meeting, 1954 January (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 26th Meeting, 1954 March (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 26th Meeting, 1954 March (Box 107, Folder 26)
  - NSF, NSB, Agendas, 1954-1955
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), National Science Board (NSB), Agenda, 27th Meeting, 1954 May (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 27th Meeting, 1954 May (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 27th Meeting, 1954 May (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 28th Meeting, 1954 August (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 28th Meeting, 1954 August (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 29th Meeting, 1954 October (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - NSF, MSB, Agenda, 29th Meeting, 1954 October (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 31st Meeting, 1954 December (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 31st Meeting, 1954 December (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 32nd Meeting, 1955 January (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 33rd Meeting, 1955 March (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - NSF, NSB, Agenda, 33rd Meeting, 1955 March (Box 108, Folder 12)